foreign
welcome back to our Channel
I am back with another interesting topic
in the Tosca automation playlist
in this session we are going to discuss
how we can synchronize execution lists
with the test cases
but first let's understand why do we
even need to synchronize this execution
list with the test cases
so whenever you make any changes to your
test cases
some of the changes are automatically
synchronized with the execution list but
some of the things are not synchronized
automatically by Tosca and you need to
synchronize them manually
but first let's discuss what is
synchronized automatically okay
so any changes which you make directly
to the test case whether you are
changing any particular test step or you
are changing any value here or if even
if you are changing the name of the test
case all these changes are synchronized
automatically in your execution list
so for example if I change the name of
this test case now okay to Execute order
you will see that the name is
automatically changed in the execution
list as well
so the changes are getting synchronized
automatically here
but some of the changes like if I uh
rename some of the test case folder or
if I move the test case to another
folder so these changes are not
automatically reflected in the execution
list
so for example if now I move this test
case to this particular new folder which
is webshop from the demo webshop okay
and if I look back at my execution list
you will see that Execute order is still
under the demo webshop folder it has not
been moved to the other folder like we
have done for the webshop right so if
now I synchronize this okay
so you will see that the test case is
gone
so that is how you can synchronize your
execution list with your test cases
changes
so you have to right click on the
execution list and then click on
synchronize okay so it will
automatically synchronize all the
changes which you have made like here so
now the test case fold the demo webshop
does not have that particular test case
right and that's what is being reflected
here it has been moved to the other
folder okay
or if I am going to put this back into
the demo webshop now okay and now let's
go back and synchronize it again to see
the change okay so it's still there
also some of the changes like uh if I
rename this folder from demo webshop to
demo shop
you will see that in the execution list
that folder has not changed right
so it is still demo webshop this is the
test case folder which is it is
referring to so it is still demo webshop
not demo shop and if now I go ahead and
synchronize this you will see it has
changed to demo shop okay
similarly if I add a new test case here
on the demo shop
okay so that particular new test case
which is present in our test case folder
is not automatically displayed under the
execution list okay you need to
synchronize whenever you are adding new
test cases to your test cases folder so
right click here again and do
synchronize and you will see the new
test case now appears here okay
so all these changes are required if you
have already created an execution list
for your test case and then you are
making those changes inside your test
cases okay it is not required if you are
still developing or if you have
completely finished your test cases
development and then you are creating an
execution list so if you don't make any
changes like adding new test cases
removing the test cases from the folder
or renaming the folders if you don't
make these kind of changes then the
synchronization is not required because
all the remaining changes what you make
in the test case would be synchronized
automatically so you don't need to go
and manually synchronize it is only
required in these three scenarios when
you change the folder names when you
remove the folders or if you add more
test cases to the test case folders so
in all of these scenarios you to
synchronize your execution list with
your test case
that's all for this particular video if
you have any questions then please leave
it in the comments if you like this
video then please subscribe to our
Channel
thanks for watching and I will see you
in the next video